question: 'What is the table that joins two models in a has-many to has-many relationship?', answer: 'Join table'
question: 'Explain how we can define Ruby regular expressions?', answer: 'A Ruby regular expression is a special sequence of characters that helps you match or find other strings.'
question: 'What is the controller action that matches the DELETE HTTP verb?', answer: '#destroy'
question: 'Explain how you can list all routes for an application?', answer: 'Write rake:routes in the terminal.'
question: 'What Rails generator is not recommended for use due to its creation of too many things?', answer: 'Scaffold'
question: 'Explain what is ORM (Object-Relationship-Model) in Rails?', answer: 'ORM indicates that your classes are mapped to the table in the database, and objects are directly mapped to the rows in the table.'
question: 'What type of params should we use in our contollers?', answer: 'Strong params'
question: 'Explain what are class libraries in Ruby?', answer: 'Class libraries in Ruby consist of a variety of domains, such as data types, thread programming, various domains, etc.'
question: 'Explain what is interpolation in Ruby?', answer: 'Ruby interpolation is the process of inserting a string into a literal.'
question: 'What is the role of Active Record in Ruby?', answer: 'Its main aim is to make sure that the relation among the object and the database is maintained and all the validations can be considered on time.'

question: '1 + 1?', answer: '2'
question: '2 x 2?', answer: '4'
question: '3 squared?', answer: '9'
question: '2 + 2?', answer: '4'
question: '3 x 3?', answer: '9'
question: '4 squared?', answer: '16'
question: '3 + 3?', answer: '6'
question: '4 x 4?', answer: '16'
question: '5 squared?', answer: '25'
question: '10 - 2?', answer: '8'